{
	"data": [
        {
            "question": "Where's Nick? He ___ be in his office.",
            "a": " might",
            "b": " mustn't",
            "c": " is to",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "3",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Take an umbrell It ___ rain later.",
            "a": " has to",
            "b": " need",
            "c": " might",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "3",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Jack ___ go to hospital yesterday.",
            "a": " must",
            "b": " had to",
            "c": " need",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "3",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "You look tire You ___ go to be",
            "a": " should",
            "b": " ought",
            "c": " are to",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "3",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ___ do it. I have already done it.",
            "a": " must not",
            "b": " need not",
            "c": " ought not",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "3",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "___ it be true?",
            "a": " Must",
            "b": " May",
            "c": " Can",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "3",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "___ we stay or leave?",
            "a": " Will",
            "b": " Would",
            "c": " Shall",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "3",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Jane was so tire She ___ have worked days and nights.",
            "a": " should",
            "b": " must",
            "c": " need",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "3",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": " I  hope she ________ it.",
            "a": "cans do",
            "b": "can does",
            "c": "can do",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "3",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": " All students ________ the TOEFL.",
            "a": "must take",
            "b": "must taking",
            "c": "must to take",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "3",
            "type": "2"
        }
    ]
}